Hinazuki was absent.
I have a bad feeling.
Hinazuki! Is someone here?!
Hinazuki!
March 3rd, 1988.
Kayo Hinazuki...
went missing.
MARCH 7TH (MONDAY)
Kayo moved to Sapporo
to live with her grandmother
for family reasons.
She's sorry she couldn't say goodbye.
I know you may all be sad, but Kayo
is happy in Sapporo, doing her best.
So, there's no reason
for anyone to feel too sad.
Hinazuki and I weren't able
to keep the last promise...
we made to each other.
I'm home.
Satoru?
I understand you're worried about Kayo...
but it's not your fault she's gone.
I...
I couldn't do anything for her.
There had to be more.
More I could've done for her.
There's only so much one person can do.
It's conceited of you
to blame yourself afterwards.
Now, come on, let's eat.
I didn't expect a second child
to go missing so soon.
WE ARE LOOKING FOR AYA NAKANISHI
The timelines are starting to converge.
AYA NAKANISHI
HIROMI SUGITA
I was overwhelmed...
by a sense of helplessness.
Bye!
KAYO HINAZUKI
It's been a week
since her disappearance.
It's not even clear if she's dead yet.
Sorry, Fujinuma...
I couldn't make your present in time.
-I'll give you your present tomorrow.
-Okay.
I promise.
Where am I?
I'm back in 2006?
I didn't do enough.
A ten-year-old child
with little knowledge and experience.
I should've realized that
and tackled the case
as if my life depended on it.
It's already come to this.
Should I step out now
and tell them the truth?
Hold on.
Black hair, 5 feet, 11 inches tall,
thin, white shirt.
Got it.
-What about the rent?
-Paid on time.
-That right?
-That's right, yes.
No.
Nobody's going to believe me,
let alone the police.
In that case...
I have to find the killer myself.
You stupid? You can't leave your phone on.
They'll track you down with GPS.
Airi.
You called me by my first name.
Are you all right?
Here.
Satoru.
I live close by.
Why don't you come with me?
Okay?
Sorry, wait here a second.
Have a seat!
Don't worry, I live alone.
-Okay.
-Make yourself comfortable.
I moved from the country
because there's a school I want to go to.
My aunt owns this property.
Oh, I see.
Are you sure about letting me in?
Judging by how you acted,
you know about the murder, don't you?
Yeah. The police came to the restaurant
asking about you.
-And it's on the news.
-Then why?
Isn't it obvious?
Because there's no way
you killed your mother.
Thank you.
By the way.
You forgot this.
JAPAN UNDERGROUND
BIG CRIMES FROM THE SHOWA PERIOD
I have something of yours!
I thought she handed me this book then.
In any case,
it seems like trouble always finds you.
Like Kayo Hinazuki's murder
on the day of the Hina Festival.
That was your hometown, wasn't it?
On the Hina Festival?
I cried when I read it.
Oh, I bet you're hungry!
I'll go out and get you something.
MARCH 3RD
The book's changed.
Was I able to change the past?
I was able to change it.
I'm back.
How can they go after him
when he's the one in the most pain?
It's so unfair.
In Funabashi City, Chiba,
a 52-year-old woman was stabbed to death
and the police are treating it
as a murder.
They are currently searching
for the victim's son,
Satoru Fujinuma,
in connection to her murder.
The incident took place
last night around 6 p.m.
In an apartment in Funabashi, Chiba,
a female was discovered dead
having been stabbed by a knife.
MANABU NISHIZONO
The police have launched
a murder investigation
and her son, Satoru Fujinuma,
who was also living in the apartment,
has not been seen since the incident.
PROTECT YOURSELF!
SELF-DEFENSE
DEFENDING YOURSELF
WITH HOUSEHOLD OBJECTS
HOW TO MAKE A STUN GUN
FROM A DISPOSABLE CAMERA.
YOUNG GIRL KIDNAPPINGS
It was an attempted kidnapping.
YOUNG GIRL KIDNAPPINGS, CHIBA
CRIMES AGAINST CHILDREN DATABASE
The key phrases for my mother's killer
are "kidnapping"
and "a man between 20 to 50."
Three years ago in the city...
A young girl was kidnapped.
I want to look into it.
It's dangerous,
but as more time passes,
my options get limited.
The sooner I do something, the better.
Thank you so much, Mr. Nishizono.
My father...
he can't believe how much business
can change with a single crosswalk.
He was very grateful.
Your father's always been so good to me.
And besides, the city council
already discussed the location.
Boss.
Excuse me.
Katagiri is heading off for the day.
Don't tell me you paid for a pizza
again?
-You could've taken it for free.
-I didn't want any special favors.
Well, I should be going now.
That Ms. Katagiri, she's very responsible
for a kid in this day and age.
She may only be 17, but she's got
a good head on her shoulders.
What is it, boss?
Here. You forgot it comes with
a free pizza.
-Thank you. You didn't have to do this.
-It's fine.
So, about Satoru...
Yes?
I still don't believe Satoru
would do something like that.
I completely agree!
If you happen to run into him,
please help him out.
If you do, give me a call
and I'll do what I can.
Okay!
I'll tell him that if I see him.
Well, bye, then.
At his first hearing,
the defendant was sentenced
to life in prison,
but he maintained his innocence.
Something doesn't feel right.
Detective Watanabe?
What were you going to tell him?
Look, I'm just worried about you.
Satoru's been accused of murder--
Then why didn't you just say so
from the start?!
You told me to help Satoru.
You said you'd help, too!
I wanted to trust you...
I'm sorry, Satoru.
My room isn't safe anymore.
Our boss found out.
No, it's okay.
You helped me get
some much needed rest.
Thank you.
Can I ask you something?
How can you trust me so much?
It's not because I can trust you...
it's because I want to trust you.
I want to trust you for myself.
It's because I want others
to trust me in return.
That's good enough for me.
You should go back to the house.
Tell the police
I threatened you to hide me.
You stupid?! I'd never say that.
Besides, you can't get away on your own.
But...
Let me just get you some money, then.
Here, speed dial one is my landline.
Call me if something happens.
Thanks.
Okay, I'll be right back.
Please wait for me.
It's not much, but it should help, right?
I should actually
distance myself from Airi for her sake.
INCOMING MESSAGE
MAILBOX
YOU HAVE NEW MAIL
You've got mail.
INBOX
FROM SACHIKO FUJINUMA
THIS IS SATORU. WAIT IN YOUR ROOM.
I'M COMING OVER NOW.
No way.
The one who has my mother's phone
is the killer!
Is this enough?
A blackout?
What? What was that?
Who's there?!
Airi!
Airi...
Don't move her!
We have to keep her still
and call an ambulance.
Satoru, go. Leave this to me.
-But--
-You involved Airi enough!
Hello?
A girl fell from the second floor.
She's unconscious.
The killer even knew where Airi lived.
He followed her.
He's a lot closer than I imagined.
Subtitle translation by
Zensho Yamamoto